Our window verified the
curse womb three hours ago.
Once 90 percent were successfully evacuated,
they made the call to seal off the center.
Road Closed
Citizens within a 500-meter radius
have been evacuated, as well.
Ijichi-san, question.
What's a "window" here?
A window is a member of
Jujutsu Tech who can see curses.
They aren't sorcerers, though.
Oh, okay.
Let's continue.
Detainee Block 2.
At present, five detainees
remain there with the curse womb.
If this curse womb is the
type that metamorphoses,
we predict it will become
a special-grade cursed spirit.
Special-grade...
Hey, so... I still don't really understand
what "special-grade" means.
Then allow me to explain it so
even idiots can understand.
*If Conventional Weapons Were Effective Against Cursed Spirits
Grade 4
A wooden bat is enough
Grade 3
If you have a handgun, you can rest easy
First, there's grade 4.
A wooden bat is enough for them.
Grade 3.
If you have a handgun, you can rest easy.
Grade 3
If you have a handgun, you can rest easy
Grade 2
Close call with a shotgun
Grade 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Even a tank may be insufficient
Grade 2.
It'll be a close call with a shotgun.
Grade 1.
Even a tank may be insufficient.
Then there's special-grade.
Close call with a shotgun
Grade 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Even a tank may be insufficient
Special-Grade
Even footing with a carpet bombing of cluster bombs\h\h\h\h\h
Let's say you might be on even footing if
you carpet bomb it with cluster bombs.
That's real bad!
Normally a jujutsu sorcerer on par with
the cursed spirit would take on the mission.
On a day like today,
that would be Gojou-sensei.
I-I see.
So where is Gojou-sensei?
Away on business.
Huh?
He's not someone who should be loafing
around at the school in the first place.
Don't expect any souvenirs.
Unfortunately, we're constantly
short-handed in this business.
You'll often have to undertake
missions beyond your power.
The current case, however,
is an abnormal one, and most urgent.
Do not fight under any circumstances.
If you encounter a special-grade,
your options are to either run or die.
Please just listen to your fears.
Do not forget that your mission here
is strictly the verification
and rescue of survivors.
Excuse me!
Excuse me, where's Tadashi?!
Stop! Stay back!
Please stay back!
Is Tadashi... Is my son Tadashi all right?!
Please calm down!
Hey, stop it!
Let go of me!
Please stay back! It's dangerous!
Let me through!
She's a guardian who was here for a visit.
Please step away.
There's a possibility that someone has
spread poisonous gas throughout the center.
We cannot share any more details at this time.
No...
Why?
Why is this happening?!
Fushiguro, Kugisaki.
We're gonna save them!
Of course we are.
Jujutsu Kaisen
Block 2
Episode 4: Curse Womb Must Die
Be careful.
I'll put up my Veil.
Emerge from darkness, blacker than darkness.
Purify that which is impure.
It's becoming night!
It's Veil.
There's a residential area nearby,
so this barrier conceals us
from the outside world.
That's incredible!
Ignorant.
Demon Dogs!
He'll let us know if the curse gets close.
Oh, I see!
Good boy, good boy! We're counting on you, okay?
Let's go.
Wait!
What is this?
Wh-What's going on in here?
This is a two-story dorm, isn't it?
C-C-Calm down! It's a maisonette.
No, it's not.
It's the deployment of an
Innate Domain due to cursed energy.
It's my first time seeing one this big.
Where's the door?!
Huh?
Th-The door's gone!
How?! We just came in
through here, didn't we?!
What do we do?
Ah, what do we do about this?
It'll be fine.
The dog remembers the scent of the entrance.
Oh, my!
Good boy! Have some jerky!
Have all the jerky you want!
You are way too calm!
You really are dependable, Fushiguro.
Thanks to you, we'll be able to
rescue people and save ourselves, too.
Let's keep moving.
Atrocious.
That's... three people, right?
Okazaki Tadashi
Is Tadashi... Is my son Tadashi all right?!
Let's take this body back.
Huh?
It's that woman's son.
But...
His face isn't too badly mangled.
His mother won't accept it if we tell
her he's dead, but we don't have a body.
We have to find and verify two more.
Leave that body behind.
Quit joking around!
We turned around, and the way
we got in here was gone!
We won't be able to come back for it later!
I didn't say to come back for it!
I said to leave it behind!
I have no intention of risking my own life
to save someone I had no intention
of saving in the first place!
No intention of saving him?
What do you mean?!
This is a juvenile detention center.
Jujutsu sorcerers are granted access to
all information about the scene beforehand.
This Okazaki Tadashi
hit a little girl on her way home from
school while driving without a license.
Youth's Name | Date of Birth
Okazaki Tadashi | August 9th, 2001
Highest Education | Sakakidate High School
Date of Detention | July 20, 2017
Family History | Only has his birth mother, Okazaki Chisaki (42)...
...gone missing, and cannot be contacted...
...living with his mother in an apartment in Eishuu City...
It was his second offense
of driving without a license.
I know you're stuck on saving lots of people
and guiding them to proper deaths.
But what are you going to do when someone
you saved kills someone else in the future?
Then why did you bother saving me?!
Cut it out!
Christ, what are you two doing?!
You're both idiots!
Think about the time and place if you—
Kugisaki?
No way! Demon Dogs should
have sensed the curse!
Itadori!
We're running!
We'll search for Kugisaki la—
There's no mistake.
It's a special-grade.
I can't move.
Move.
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Help others.
Itadori?
Huh?
Damn it, where am I?
It's so dark, I can't see a thing.
The curse's presence!
How can there be so many?!
Nue!
Don't die on me, Itadori and Kugisaki!
I can't escape after it's gotten this close!
Hey, Sukuna!
If I die, you die too, right?
If you don't want that, then help me out!
Nope!
Even if the parts of me inside you die,
there are eighteen other fragments of my soul.
Still, irritatingly enough,
I don't have control of this body.
If you want to switch, go ahead and switch.
But once you do,
I'll kill that brat before the cursed spirit can!
Then I'll go for that woman!
She's a lively one. I'll have fun with her.
I'm not going to let you do that.
I bet.
But if you're too focused on me,
your friends are gonna die.
It's not jujutsu.
He just unleashed pure cursed energy.
Fushiguro!
Take Kugisaki and get out of here!
I'll keep this one busy
until you two are out.
As soon as you're out,
give me some kind of signal.
Once you do... I'll switch with Sukuna.
You know you can't do that!
Not with only one arm against a special-grade!
Look closer.
It's having fun.
It's obviously toying with us.
I can at least buy us some time.
No!
Fushiguro!
Please.
Demon Dogs!
Find Kugisaki!
This is my last one.
I should've brought a lot more with me.
Trying to say it's easier to move
around in your underwear?
What do I do, though?
I have no clue how to use cursed energy.
But for now, that's fine.
I just have to buy ti—
What was that? A cursed energy barrier?
Ow, ow, ow...
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts! Why am I...
If only I hadn't picked up
that finger back then...
If I hadn't eaten it...
If only...
Stop!
Don't think!
No! No!
I want to run! I want to run! I want to run!
I don't want to die!
If I died here...
If I actually died...
Would that be a proper death?!
Don't think!
Help others.
Have I...
gotten so weak?
I know your face now.
I swear I'll curse you!
We're escaping, Kugisaki!
I hate frogs, you know.
Yeah, well, sorry!
I was so full of myself.
I thought I was strong.
I thought I was at least strong
enough to choose when I died.
But I was wrong.
I'm weak!
I'm far too weak!
Augh, I don't want to die!
No! No way!
But... I am going to die!
A proper death?
Yeah, right! Don't be naïve!
Jujutsu sorcerers never die without regret.
Still, I want to be able to say
my death was a proper one.
The negative emotions of mankind
become the source of curses.
So all the hate, fear, regret...
Let it all out...
And put it in your fist!
Damn it!
That howl...
It's Fushiguro's signal.
What a thoroughly annoying brat.
Jujutsu Kaisen
He's obviously screwing with me.
Hold on a moment. I'm thinking right now.
What can I do to make that brat regret this?
If I went after him, the brat would
just switch back right beforehand.
So the thing that would cause
him the most trouble...
is probably this.
I'll put things back the way they were.
Hey, let's go kill some kids.
Follow me.
Idiot.
Ah, shit. I healed this one, too.
You don't like walks?
Well, cursed spirits are usually
supposed to stay where they're born.
Fine, fine. In that case...
you die here!
Hey, what's the matter?
You're not finished already, are you?
That's it. Come on, try harder.
Even a cursed spirit
would miss their arm, right?
Please expand the evacuation
area to ten kilometers.
What about you?
I'm waiting here for Itadori to return.
I see.
After I take Kugisaki-san to the hospital,
I'll return as quickly as possible.
No, there wouldn't be much
point in you staying here.
If you want to do something,
please ask them to send over
a sorcerer grade 1 or higher.
Not that I imagine any are around.
I'll do what I can. Later.
If the worst case happens...
I don't want to let him die.
They are.
Please do something about this.
...then it's my responsibility to end him.
Hey, did you know?
We're both classified as
special-grade, apparently.
Both you and me, man.
Good job, special-grade.
Keep trying.
You look happy.
Want me to praise you?
But healing with cursed energy isn't that hard
for cursed spirits, unlike for humans.
Neither you nor this brat
really understand
what curses truly are.
This is a good opportunity,
so I'll show you...
what real jujutsu is.
Domain Expansion.
Malevolent Shrine!
I was planning to cut you in three slices,
but you're really weak.
Oh, yeah, and then there's this.
I'll be taking this.
It's over.
This sucks!
If you're gonna switch, just do it already!
What's the matter, brat?
Juju Stroll
Yes, yes, understood.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Stare...
What's the matter?
You bow while on the phone.
I just get so wrapped up in creating the feeling
of "I'm on the phone!" while on a call...
I know what you mean.
I've hurt my neck several times dealing
with ingrown hairs while depilating.
Of course, I've hurt my pores, too.
Is that really the same?
You're often irritated when
you're on the phone, Fushiguro.
That's because of Gojou-sensei,
not the phone.
You often wander around when
you're on the phone, Itadori.
Speaking of phones,
can you all stay on a call while holding
the phone against your shoulder?
Episode 5:
Curse Womb Must Die -II-
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org